PHONE : +66 094 052 8596

EMAIL : Wasinmekkit@gmail.com

ADDRESS: 230/6405 Chaengwattana Rd. Laksi Area,

Bangkok, Thailand, 10210



Front End Developer



Visit My Website



https://bit.lv/wasin-mekki

PROFILE

With 5 years of experience in web development and design, I am a creative and versatile Front End Developer. HTML, CSS, SCSS, Javascript, and modern libraries and frameworks are all required. Proficient in UI/UX design and motion graphics. Digital marketing, Programmatic Advertising, and Search engine optimization are all fields about which I am highly enthusiastic.

EXPERTISE

- Website Development
- UX/UI Design
- · Graphic Design
- · Motion Graphic
- Animation
- Search engine optimization
- · Digital Marketing
- Serverless Computing
- Programmatic Advertising

EDUCATION

2015 - 2017

Bachelor's Degree in Information Technology

North Bangkok University

2012 - 2015

Diploma Vocational Certificate in Information Technology

Siam Business Administration Technological College

REFERENCE

Mr. Paisan Sa-nguansin

Web Management and Monetization Manager **Advanced Info Service PLC.** Paisansa@ais.co.th

Mr. Anucha Sanu

Senior Web Developer North Bangkok University Anucha.sa@northbkk.ac.th

Experience

2018 - Present

Front End Developer | Advanced Info Service PLC.

Working as a Front End Developer. I created a variety of websites for organizations in the telecommunications industry using HTML, CSS, Sass, JavaScript, and Adobe AEM as CMS. I contributed to the company's developer experience by implementing tools and technologies to improve our development process. And contributed with my team to improve UX/UI design to increase the efficiency of the customer journey. In addition, website optimization and Programmatic Advertising Platforms such as Cloudflare worker, Adobe DTM, Adobe Analytics, Adnuntius, Relay42, and Cxense.

2017 - 2018

Web Developer & Public Relations | North Bangkok University

As a Web Developer & Public Relations. I contributed to the development of the university website. Including university data management system, Alumni website, and database management system, Online sales tracking system and summarized as a report using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, SQL plus modern libraries and frameworks. And also to work on the production of advertising media such as motion graphics, Banners, Google Ads, Social media Ads to boost online sales and increase university website traffic.

2016 - 2017

Software Technician | ICOM TECH CO.,LTD

My primary responsibility as a Software Technician was to support and advise clients. In terms of software applications as well as problem-solving. This includes software installation and client training. In addition, technical and manual preparation support and consultation to the sales team.

AWARDS

2020

Honorable Mention award

Animation@Work 2020 from Reallusion.

201

Glare Outstanding Work

Asiagraph Reallusion Animation Award From Asiagraph.

2017

First Runner-up award

Toyota moving challenge Animation Contest.

2015

Winner Award and Popular vote

Thailand Animation Contest From NECTEC.